netexam.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Netexam

**Website Privacy Policy**

Last modified: September 26, 2019

**Introduction**

Media Defined, Inc., doing business as NetExam, together with its affiliates, including subsidiaries and entities that Media Defined, Inc. operates (collectively, “Media Defined,” “us” or “we”), provides cloud-based sales, marketing, learning, and customer experience solutions. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. 

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website [http://www.netexam.com/](http://www.netexam.com/) (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. 

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website;
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website;
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website;
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy; and
  * Through surveys that we may conduct on this Website from time to time in which you voluntarily participate.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 16**

Our Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website or through any of its features, register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please Contact Us.

California residents under 16 years of age may have additional rights regarding the collection and sale of their personal information. Please see Your California Privacy Rights for more information.

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“personal information”).
  * That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as any Media Defined products and services you utilize, geographic locations, and general demographics.
  * About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site, which may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

**_Information You Provide to Us_**

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service(s), posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Website or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

**_Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies_**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). For information on how you can opt out of behavioral tracking on this website and how we respond to web browser signals and other mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about behavioral tracking, please Contact Us.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information. We may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Website and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

**Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies [alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies] to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you;
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us;
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
  * To provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices;
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it;
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website;
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information; and/or
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please contact us using the information in the “Contact Information” section below. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy: 

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Media Defined’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Media Defined about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have [consented to/not opted out of] these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an email address to use the “email a friend” feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that email and your email address to the recipients.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:>

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Media Defined, our customers, or others, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s [website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising.** If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending us an email with your request to [privacy@mediadefined.com.](mailto:privacy@mediadefined.com)]
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your [email address/contact information] used by Media Defined to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [privacy@mediadefined.com](mailto:privacy@mediadefined.com). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to us as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.
  * **Targeted Advertising.** If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [privacy@mediadefined.com](mailto:privacy@mediadefined.com)

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s [website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see Your California Privacy Rights for more information.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page, if offered.

You may also send us an email at [privacy@mediadefined.com](mailto:privacy@mediadefined.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, r might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our terms of use.

California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see Your California Privacy Rights for more information.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit [https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa](https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa).

**Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the primary email address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Us**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us by email at [privacy@mediadefined.com](mailto:privacy@mediadefined.com), or in writing addressed to: 

Media Defined, Inc.   
3002A Commerce Street   
Dallas, Texas 75026

In addition, Media Defined has designated the International Centre for Dispute Resolution, the international division of the American Arbitration Association (ICDR/AAA), as an independent recourse mechanism to investigate and resolve disputes at no cost to you. To register a complaint or concern with the ICDR/AAA, please visit <http://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html>.

**Privacy Shield Policy**

This Privacy Shield Policy (“Policy”) describes how Media Defined, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates in the United States (“Media Defined,” “we,” or “us”) collect, use, and disclose certain personally identifiable information that we receive in the United States (“U.S.”) from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and the United Kingdom (“U.K.”) (“Personal Data”). This Policy applies to the following U.S. affiliated entities: Media Defined, Inc. This Policy supplements our Website Privacy Policy, and unless specifically defined in this Policy, the terms in this Policy have the same meaning as the Website Privacy Policy.

Media Defined, Inc. recognizes that the EEA and the U.K. have established strict protections regarding the handling of Personal Data, including requirements to provide adequate protection for Personal Data transferred outside of the EEA and the U.K.. To provide adequate protection for certain Personal Data about consumers, corporate customers, clients, suppliers, business partners, job applicants, and employees received in the U.S. from the EEA and the U.K., Media Defined has elected to self-certify to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework administered by the U.S. Department of Commerce (“Privacy Shield”). Media Defined adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement, and Liability.

For purposes of enforcing compliance with the Privacy Shield, Media Defined is subject to the investigatory and enforcement authority of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. For more information about the Privacy Shield, see the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield website located at: [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). To review Media Defined’s representation on the Privacy Shield list, see the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield self-certification list located at: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

**Personal Data Collection and Use**

Our Website Privacy Policy describes the categories of Personal Data that we may receive in the U.S. as well as the purposes for which we use that Personal Data. Media Defined will only process Personal Data in ways that are compatible with the purpose for which Media Defined collected it, or for purposes the individual later authorizes. Before we use your Personal Data for a purpose that is materially different than the purpose for which we collected it or that you later authorized, we will provide you with the opportunity to opt out. Media Defined maintains reasonable procedures to help ensure that Personal Data is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.

**Data Transfers to Third Parties**

 ** _Third-Party Agents or Service Providers._** We may transfer Personal Data to our third-party agents or service providers who perform functions on our behalf as described in our Website Privacy Policy. Where required by the Privacy Shield, we enter into written agreements with those third-party agents and service providers requiring them to provide the same level of protection the Privacy Shield requires and limiting their use of the data to the specified services provided on our behalf. We take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure that third-party agents and service providers process Personal Data in accordance with our Privacy Shield obligations and to stop and remediate any unauthorized processing. Under certain circumstances, we may remain liable for the acts of our third-party agents or service providers who perform services on our behalf for their handling of Personal Data that we transfer to them.

**_Third-Party Data Controllers._** In some cases, we may transfer Personal Data to unaffiliated third-party data controllers. These third parties do not act as agents or service providers and are not performing functions on our behalf. We will only provide your Personal Data to third-party data controllers where you have not opted-out of such disclosures, or in the case of sensitive Personal Data, where you have opted-in if the Privacy Shield requires consent. We enter into written contracts with any unaffiliated third-party data controllers requiring them to provide the same level of protection for Personal Data the Privacy Shield requires. We also limit their use of your Personal Data so that it is consistent with any consent you have provided and with the notices you have received. If we transfer your Personal Data to one of our affiliated entities within our corporate group, we will take steps to ensure that your Personal Data is protected with the same level of protection the Privacy Shield requires.

**_Disclosures for National Security or Law Enforcement._** Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your Personal Data in response to valid requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

**Security**

Media Defined maintains reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect Personal Data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction in accordance with the Privacy Shield.

**Access Rights**

You may have the right to access the Personal Data that we hold about you and to request that we correct, amend, or delete it if it is inaccurate or processed in violation of the Privacy Shield. These access rights may not apply in some cases, including where providing access is unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances or where it would violate the rights of someone other than the individual requesting access. If you would like to request access to, correction, amendment, or deletion of your Personal Data, you can submit a written request to the contact information provided below. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity. In some circumstances we may charge a reasonable fee for access to your information.

**Questions or Complaints**

In compliance with the Privacy Shield principles, you can Contact Us regarding any questions or complaints about the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Data. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints or disputes regarding the use or disclosure of your Personal Data within 45 days of receiving your complaint. For any unresolved complaints, we have agreed to cooperate with the ICDR/AAA. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Media Defined at Contact Us. If you are unsatisfied with the resolution of your complaint, you may contact the ICDR/AAA at [http://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html for further information and assistance](http://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html).

**_Binding Arbitration._** Media Defined has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to the American Arbitration Association, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States, You may have the option to select binding arbitration for the resolution of your complaint under certain circumstances, provided you have taken the following steps: (1) raised your complaint directly with Media Defined and provided us the opportunity to resolve the issue; (2) made use of the independent dispute resolution mechanism identified above; and (3) raised the issue through the relevant data protection authority and allowed the U.S. Department of Commerce an opportunity to resolve the complaint at no cost to you. For more information on binding arbitration, see [U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield Framework: Annex I (Binding Arbitration)](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction). If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit the American Arbitration Association at <https://www.adr.org/> for more information or to file a complaint. The services of American Arbitration Association shall be provided at no cost to you by Media Defined, as applicable.

To ask questions or comment about Privacy Shield compliance and practices or to make a complaint, contact us by email at [privacy@mediadefined.com](mailto:privacy@mediadefined.com), or in writing addressed to

Media Defined, Inc.   
3002A Commerce Street   
Dallas, Texas 75026

 **Changes to This Policy**

We reserve the right to amend this Policy from time to time consistent with the Privacy Shield’s requirements.

**Effective date: October 5, 2019**

**Last modified: October 5, 2019**
